There was a man, two men sitting at a crossroads, right? Two streets, two ways. And somebody walked
up and said, what's it like up the street? Place I came from, people were horrible, hateful, nasty,
mean people, just whatever. And the guy said, hey, hate to tell you, that's exactly what you're
going to find up the road. Next person came up, what's it like up the road? Where I come from,
everybody's loving and kind and they treat everybody good. Well, that's exactly what you're
going to find up the road. Good for you. And the other guys, they're going to the same place.
You find what you see and seek and believe. When I go somewhere, I don't think about how
is this going to be horrible or how is this going to be drudgery? Every time I leave my house, I'm
like, what amazing thing is going to happen today? I'm believing that something wonderful is going to
happen every day. And that's exactly what I see and I find. So when I see someone that's in the
space where they can't see beyond it, it's like, well, Precious, we're going to talk about what's
going on with you. We'll talk about it. Yeah. If you genuinely open yourself up and they know that
it's safe, if it is something inside, they'll let it out and then they can build another pathway for
themselves.